<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.5" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.5" modifiedDate="2017-04-15T19:59:44">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>HP96 Christians, awake, salute the happy morn</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines><br/>Christians, awake, salute the happy morn,<br/>Whereon the Saviour of mankind was born:<br/>Rise to adore the mystery of love,<br/>Which hosts of angels chanted from above;<br/>With them the joyful tidings first begun<br/>Of God incarnate and the Virgin's Son.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines><br/>Then to the watchful shepherds it was told,<br/>Who heard the angelic herald's voice: Behold,<br/>I bring good tidings of a Saviour's birth<br/>To you and all the nations upon earth:<br/>This day hath God fulfilled His promised word,<br/>This day is born a Saviour, Christ the Lord.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines><br/>He spake; and straightway the celestial choir<br/>In hymns of joy, unknown before, conspire,<br/>The praises of redeeming love they sang,<br/>And heaven's whole orb with hallelujahs rang;<br/>God's highest glory was their anthem still,<br/>Peace upon earth, and unto men good-will.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines><br/>To Bethlehem straight the enlightened shepherds ran,<br/>To see the wonder God had wrought for man:<br/>Then to their flocks, still praising God, return,<br/>And their glad hearts with holy rapture burn;<br/>Amazed, the wondrous tidings they proclaim,<br/>The first apostles of His infant fame.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines><br/>O may we keep and ponder in our mind<br/>God's wondrous love in saving lost mankind;<br/>Trace we the Babe, who hath retrieved our loss,<br/>From the poor manger to the bitter Cross;<br/>Tread in His steps, assisted by His grace,<br/>Till man's first heavenly state again takes place.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines><br/>Then may we hope, the angelic hosts among,<br/>To sing, redeemed, a glad triumphal song;<br/>He that was born upon this joyful day<br/>Around us all His glory shall display;<br/>Saved by His love, incessant we shall sing<br/>Eternal praise to heaven's almighty King.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
