<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2018-12-09T19:17:55">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>SF195 Christians, awake, salute the happy morn</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>John Byrom (1692-1763)</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines><br/>Christians, awake, salute the happy morn<br/>whereon the Saviour of the world was born;<br/>rise to adore the mystery of love,<br/>which hosts of angels chanted from above;<br/>with them the joyful tidings first begun<br/>of God incarnate and the Virgin's Son.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines><br/>Then to the watchful shepherds it was told,<br/>who heard the angelic herald's voice, 'Behold,<br/>I bring good tidings of a Saviour's birth<br/>to you and all the nations upon earth;<br/>this day has God fulfilled his promised word,<br/>this day is born a Saviour, Christ the Lord.'</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines><br/>He spoke;and straightway the celestial choir<br/>in hymns of joy, unknown before, conspire.<br/>The praises of redeeming love they sang,<br/>and heaven's whole orb with alleluias rang;<br/>God's highest glory was their anthem still,<br/>peace on the earth, in every heart goodwill.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines><br/>To Bethl'em straight the enlightened shepherds ran,<br/>to see, unfolding, God's eternal plan;<br/>then to their flocks, still praising God, return,<br/>and their glad hearts with holy rapture burn;<br/>amazed, the wondrous tidings they proclaim,<br/>the first apostles of his infant fame.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines><br/>Like Mary, let us ponder in our mind<br/>God's wondrous love in saving humankind;<br/>trace we the Babe, who has retrieved our loss,<br/>from his poor manger to his bitter cross;<br/>treading his steps, assisted by his grace,<br/>till our first heavenly state again takes place.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines><br/>Then may we hope, the angelic hosts among,<br/>to sing, redeemed, a glad triumphal song;<br/>he who was born upon this joyful day<br/>around us all his glory shall display;<br/>saved by his love, incessant we shall sing<br/>eternal praise to heaven's almighty King.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
