<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2018-11-12T16:36:57">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>SF409 Let us build a house where love can dwell</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines><br/>Let us build a house where love can dwell<br/>and all can safely live,<br/>a place where saints and children tell<br/>how hearts learn to forgive.<br/>Built of hopes and dreams and visions,<br/>rock of faith and vault of grace;<br/>here the love of Christ shall end divisions:<br/>All are welcome, all are welcome,<br/>all are welcome in this place.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines><br/>Let us build a house where prophets speak,<br/>and words are strong and true,<br/>where all God's children dare to seek<br/>to dream God's reign anew.<br/>Here the cross shall stand as witness<br/>and as symbol of God's grace;<br/>here as one we claim the faith of Jesus;<br/>All are welcome, all are welcome,<br/>all are welcome in this place.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines><br/>Let us build a house where love is found<br/>in water, wine and wheat:<br/>a banquet hall on holy ground,<br/>where peace and justice meet.<br/>Here the love of God through Jesus,<br/>is revealed in time and space;<br/>as we share in Christ the feast that frees us:<br/>All are welcome, all are welcome,<br/>all are welcome in this place.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines><br/>Let us build a house where hands will reach<br/>beyond the wood and stone<br/>to heal and strengthen, serve and teach,<br/>and live the Word they've known.<br/>Here the outcast and the stranger<br/>bear the image of God's face;<br/>let us bring an end to fear and danger:<br/>All are welcome, all are welcome,<br/>all are welcome in this place.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines><br/>Let us build a house where all are named,<br/>their songs and visions heard<br/>and loved and treasured, taught and claimed<br/>as words within the Word.<br/>Built of tears and cries and laughter,<br/>prayers of faith and songs of grace,<br/>let this house proclaim from floor to rafter:<br/>All are welcome, all are welcome,<br/>all are welcome in this place.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
