<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2018-12-09T19:21:15">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>SF461 Come, O thou Traveller unknown,</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>Charles Wesley (1707-1788)</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines><br/>Come, O thou Traveller unknown,<br/>whom still I hold, but cannot see!<br/>My company before is gone,<br/>and I am left alone with thee;<br/>with thee all night I mean to stay,<br/>and wrestle till the break of day.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines><br/>I need not tell thee who I am,<br/>my misery and sin declare;<br/>thyself hast called me by my name;<br/>look on thy hands, and read it there:<br/>but who, I ask thee, who art thou?<br/>Tell me thy name, and tell me now.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines><br/>In vain thou strugglest to get free;<br/>I never will unloose my hold!<br/>Art thou the Man that died for me?<br/>The secret of thy love unfold:<br/>wrestling, I will not let thee go,<br/>till I thy name, thy nature know.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines><br/>Wilt thou not yet to me reveal<br/>thy new, unutterable name?<br/>Tell me, I still beseech thee, tell;<br/>to know it now resolved I am:<br/>wrestling, I will not let thee go,<br/>till I thy name, thy nature know.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines><br/>What though my shrinking flesh complain,<br/>and murmur to contend so long?<br/>I rise superior to my pain,<br/>when I am weak, then I am strong;<br/>and when my all of strength shall fail,<br/>I shall with the God-Man prevail.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines><br/>Yield to me now;for I am weak,<br/>but confident in self-despair;<br/>speak to my heart, in blessings speak,<br/>be conquered by my instant prayer;<br/>speak, or thou never hence shalt move,<br/>and tell me if thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines><br/>'Tis Love! 'Tis Love! Thou diedst for me!<br/>I hear thy whisper in my heart;<br/>the morning breaks, the shadows flee,<br/>pure, universal love thou art;<br/>to me, to all, thy mercies move:<br/>thy nature and thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines><br/>My prayer has power with God;the grace<br/>unspeakable I now receive;<br/>through faith I see thee face to face,<br/>I see thee face to face, and live!<br/>In vain I have not wept and strove:<br/>thy nature and thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines><br/>I know thee, Saviour, who thou art,<br/>Jesus, the feeble sinner's friend;<br/>nor wilt thou with the night depart,<br/>but stay and love me to the end;<br/>thy mercies never shall remove:<br/>thy nature and thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines><br/>The Sun of Righteousness on me<br/>has risen with healing in his wings;<br/>withered my nature's strength, from thee<br/>my soul its life and succour brings;<br/>my help is all laid up above:<br/>thy nature and thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines><br/>Contented now upon my thigh<br/>I halt, till life's short journey end;<br/>all helplessness, all weakness, I<br/>on thee alone for strength depend;<br/>nor have I power from thee to move:<br/>thy nature and thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines><br/>Lame as I am, I take the prey,<br/>hell, earth, and sin with ease o'ercome;<br/>I leap for joy, pursue my way,<br/>and as a bounding hart fly home,<br/>through all eternity to prove<br/>thy nature and thy name is Love.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
