<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.6" modifiedDate="2018-12-09T19:21:47">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>SF745 For all the saints who from their labours rest,</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>William Walsham How (1823-1867)</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines><br/>For all the saints who from their labours rest,<br/>who thee by faith before the world confessed,<br/>thy name, O Jesus, be for ever blest:<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines><br/>Thou wast their rock, their fortress and their might;<br/>thou, Lord, their captain in the well-fought fight;<br/>thou in the darkness still their one true light:<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines><br/>O may thy soldiers, faithful, true, and bold,<br/>fight as the saints who nobly fought of old,<br/>and win, with them, the victor's crown of gold!<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines><br/>O blest communion, fellowship divine!<br/>We feebly struggle, they in glory shine;<br/>yet all are one in thee, for all are thine:<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines><br/>And when the strife is fierce, the warfare long,<br/>steals on the ear the distant triumph song,<br/>and hearts are brave again, and arms are strong:<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines><br/>The golden evening brightens in the west;<br/>soon, soon to faithful warriors comes their rest;<br/>sweet is the calm of paradise the blest:<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines><br/>But lo, there breaks a yet more glorious day:<br/>the saints triumphant rise in bright array;<br/>the King of Glory passes on his way!<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines><br/>From earth's wide bounds, from ocean's farthest coast,<br/>through gates of pearl streams in the countless host,<br/>singing to Father, Son, and Holy Ghost:<br/>Alleluia, alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
