<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4.5" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4.5" modifiedDate="2017-04-15T20:06:08">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>SF92 Think of a world without any flowers</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Doreen E Newport</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any flowers,<br/>think of a wood without any trees,<br/>think of a sky without any sunshine,<br/>think of the air without any breeze;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for flowers and trees and sunshine;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any animals,<br/>think of a field without any herd,<br/>think of a stream without any fishes,<br/>think of a dawn without any bird:<br/>we thank you, Lord, for all your living creatures;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any paintings,<br/>think of a room where all the walls are bare,<br/>think of a rainbow without any colours,<br/>think of the earth with darkness everywhere;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for paintings and for colours;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any poetry,<br/>think of a book without any words,<br/>think of a song without any music,<br/>think of a hymn without any verse;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for poetry and music;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any science,<br/>think of a journey with nothing to explore,<br/>think of a quest without any mystery,<br/>nothing to seek and nothing left in store;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for miracles of science;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any people,<br/>think of a street with no-one living there,<br/>think of a town without any houses,<br/>no-one to love and nobody to care;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for families and friendships;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines><br/>Think of a world without any worship,<br/>think of a God without his only Son,<br/>think of a cross without resurrection,<br/>only a grave and not a victory won;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for showing us our Saviour;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines><br/>Thanks to our Lord for being here among us,<br/>thanks be to him for sharing all we do,<br/>thanks for our Church and all the love we find here,<br/>thanks for this place and all its promise true;<br/>we thank you, Lord, for life in all its richness;<br/>we thank you, Lord, and praise your holy name.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
